-Is the bank worried.
Then they want higher interest rates and maybe stop lending more.
Fast -growing real estate companies need a lot of money to continue buying new.
What do they do when they can't get more loans?
Well, then they give out a preference share.
There are special shares that are over ordinary shares.
They simply ask investors for money.
In return, they receive dividends.
"Give us money now, we give back a little at a time and even more."
Type as a loan.
But preference shares are not counted as loans.
They instead end up on equity-
-Fastän they are rather something between loans and shares.
Then there are D shares.
They are not as strong as preference shares-